http://www.worldhum.com/info/privacy-policy/

World Hum
The best travel stories on the internet.
Travel Blog
Travel Blog Homepage »
Shrinking Planet
R.I.P.
Go
Home»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
WorldHum.com Privacy Policy
PLEASE NOTE THAT OUR PRIVACY POLICY HAS CHANGED EFFECTIVE OCTOBER 15, 2010.
World Hum, and its subsidiaries and affiliated entities (collectively, “WH,” “we,” and “us”) respect your privacy and we want you to understand the ways in which we do and do not use the information that you transmit when you visit our websites. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the websites where it is posted (collectively, the “Sites”). BY USING THE SITES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SITES.
The web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we’ll post the changes here. You can tell when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last Updated” legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy. If WH materially changes how it uses your personally identifiable information, we will notify you via e-mail. Use of the Sites following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect.
Thanks for making our Sites a part of your discoveries online!
What Information We Collect
The information gathered through our Sites falls into two categories: (1) personally identifiable information voluntarily supplied by users to our Sites through optional registration or other methods and (2) non-personally identifiable information that is routinely gathered as users navigate through our Sites as well as supplied to us by users.
Personally Identifiable Information
Certain elements of our Sites may require the submission of personally identifiable information, such as your name, company, address, telephone number, e-mail address, or other information that is not publicly available.
The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary, but, we may be unable to provide you with services we make available to other users to our Sites if you choose not to provide us with personally identifiable information.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We and/or our third-party service providers collect non-personally identifiable information, which does not identify you, when you interact with our Sites.
Click here: http://www.nielsen-netratings.com/privacy/sitecensus.htm to learn more information about one way in which we use a third party service to collect and use information on our Website.
Non-personally identifiable information is generally collected as follows:
Cookies
To help make our Sites more responsive to the needs of our users, we or our third-party service providers may invoke a standard feature found in browser software, called a “cookie,” to assign each user a unique, random number, a sort of anonymous user ID that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn’t actually identify the user; it just identifies the computer that a user uses to access our Sites. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won’t know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personally identifiable information a cookie can contain is information you supply.
We use cookies to help us tailor our Sites to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service. In addition, we may use cookies to track the pages on our Sites visited by our users. We can improve our Sites if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users to our Sites.
Some of the cookies we use may be “flash” cookies or Adobe cookies.  A Flash cookie is a data file placed on a Computer via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Computer.  While they are harmless, depending on your browser, these cookies may not be deleted when your cookies are deleted, and in some instances, they may cause your cookies to reappear in your browser.  Please check your browser to determine where these types of cookies are stored and how they may be deleted.
Web Beacons
We or our third-party service providers may use software technology called “web beacons” (also known as “clear gifs,” “web bugs” or “pixel tags”) or other similar technologies in connection with our Sites. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of our Sites and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When used in HTML-formatted e-mail messages, web beacons can tell the sender whether and when the e-mail has been opened. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Web beacons do not collect personally identifiable information.
IP Addresses
Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our Sites. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data - such as the webpages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our webpages to you upon request, to tailor our Sites to the interests of our users and to measure traffic within our Sites.
How Information Collected On Our Sites Is Used and Shared
Personally Identifiable Information
WH uses your personally identifiable information for the purposes for which you have provided it to us, such as providing you with services you request in connection with our Sites, offering you access to password-protected portions of our Sites, customizing the advertising and content you see on our Sites, and improving our products and services. In addition, we may share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third-party service providers who help us maintain our Sites and provide other administrative services including, but not limited to, order processing and fulfillment, providing customer service, maintaining and analyzing data, sending customer communications on behalf of WH, and the administration and fulfillment of contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions. Because the unaffiliated third-party service providers that help us administer our Sites may have access to users’ personally identifiable information, if you do not wish for such unaffiliated third-party service providers to have access to your information, please do not register or submit any personally identifiable information to us. Of course, you are always free to use our Sites anonymously.
We may use your personally identifiable information to contact you via e-mail to confirm your registration with our Sites or to inform you of changes to this Privacy Policy or our Visitor Agreement. Because this information may be critical to your use of our Sites, you may not opt out of receiving these e-mails.
We may share your information with our affiliates, joint marketing and strategic partners and other unaffiliated third parties for research, administrative and internal business purposes, as well as for their marketing purposes. If you would prefer that we do not share your information with third-party marketers, please notify us by opting-out of having your information shared for such purposes in your account preferences and/or when you register for an account on our Sites. You may change your preferences at a later date or request that we delete your information (see Accessing Your Information and Changing Your Elections below).
Sometimes, we may contact you directly about our own or others’ products and services, and we may also combine information we receive from you through our Sites with outside records to enhance our ability to market products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you’d prefer that we do not contact you regarding third party products and services, please notify us by opting-out of having your information shared for such purposes in your account preferences and/or when you register on our Sites. And remember, you can change your preferences or request that we delete your information at any time (see Accessing Your Information and Changing Your Elections below).
In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of our assets relating to our Sites are sold or transferred to another party, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, your personally identifiable information may be transferred to this acquiring entity. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if we believe we are required to do so in order to comply with law (including court orders and subpoenas); to comply with requests from law enforcement agencies or the government; to enforce our Visitor Agreement; to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and the rights, privacy, safety or property of our employees or other users of our Sites; to protect our operations; and to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Because non-personally identifiable information does not identify you, we reserve the right to use it for any purpose, and to share it with third parties for any purpose. For example, we may present information such as aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our Sites to our advertisers to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our Sites. Please note that to the extent any non-personally identifiable information is combined with personally identifiable information, the combined information will be treated as personally identifiable information for as long as it is so combined.
Third-Party Sites
You should note that our Sites include links to other websites that may have privacy policies and practices that differ from ours. If you can’t find the privacy policy of a third party website via a link from the website’s homepage, you should contact the website directly for more information. We encourage everyone to be proactive in understanding how their information is collected and used online.
Third-Party Advertisers
We may use third-party advertisers to serve advertisements on our Sites. Please be advised that such advertisers may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to, among other things, enable such advertisers to monitor which ads have been served to your browser and which webpages you were viewing when such ads were delivered.  PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT COVER THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY ADVERTISERS.
Forums, Chat Rooms and Other Public Posting Areas
Please note that any information you include in a message you post to any chat room, forum or other public posting area on our Sites is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don’t want people to know your e-mail address, for example, don’t include it in any message you post publicly on our Sites. PLEASE BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS ON OUR SITES. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION THAT YOU DISCLOSE IN CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS ON OUR SITES.
Accessing Your Information and Changing Your Elections
If you want to change your election on how we use or share your personally identifiable information, or you wish to review, update, or delete the information you have provided us, please contact us at: Privacy_Policy@worldhum.com
.
Children’s Privacy
WH recognizes the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 13. Our Sites do not target and are not intended for children under the age of 13. WH does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and, if we learn that we have received personally identifiable information from a child, we will remove this information from our database.
Security
WH seeks to safeguard the personally identifiable information you provide. As effective as our safeguards are, no security system is completely impenetrable. Please be assured, however, that WH takes reasonable security measures to protect user information under our company’s control against loss, misuse, or alteration.
Miscellaneous
The Sites are controlled and operated by us from the United States, and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Please note that we do not represent or warrant that the Sites are appropriate or available for use in any jurisdiction outside of the United States. Those who choose to access the Sites do so on their own initiative and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.
If you are visiting the Sites from a county or jurisdiction outside of the United States, please note that the United States may not have the same data protection laws as your country of residence. By providing your personally identifiable information to WH, you consent to: (i) the use of your personally identifiable information for the uses described in this Privacy Policy; and (ii) the transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States.
WH disclaims, and you agree, that WH will not be liable to you for any damages caused by acts or events beyond our reasonable control including, without limitation, acts of God, fires, floods, acts of terrorism, wars, civil disturbances, sabotage, accidents, labor disputes, governmental actions, and failures or delays of transportation that result in our disclosure of your personally identifiable information.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding WH’s disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to Privacy_Policy@worldhum.com
or send written correspondence to the address listed under Contact Us below, attention California Privacy Rights.
Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at Privacy_Policy@worldhum.com
. Please note that e-mail communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly, you should not include sensitive information in your e-mail correspondence with us.
World Hum
c/o The Travel Channel, L.L.C.
5425 Wisconsin Avenue
Chevy Chase, MD 20815
Attn:  Legal Affairs
(c)2010 The Travel Channel, L.L.C.  All Rights Reserved.
Travel Blog
2016 Book Passage Travel Writers & Photographers...
R.I.P. SkyMall?
01.29.15 | 8:09 AM ET
Read entire travel blog »
Join the Discussion
Email Your Tip
Got a suggestion? Send it to: .(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address)
See all destinations »
